(Sheldon:)But we need a cryogenic
centrifugal pump.
(Leonard:)Well, forget it!
It's not gonna happen.
(Sheldon:)Well, come now, Leonard,
this may be your only chance
(Sheldon:)to make a real contribution
to science!
I repeat: Not gonna happen.
(Penny:)What was all that
about me trading sexual favors
(Penny:)for material gain?
(Sheldon:)It was a compliment.
(Sheldon:)I believe in giving credit
where credit is due.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Okay, fine. I'll tell him.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Leonard, Mrs. Latham's car
is here for you.
I won't be too late;
I'm just gonna make
(Leonard:)a final pitch for the funding
and then say good night.
(Sheldon:)Hold on,
I have something for you.
(Leonard:)What's this?
(Sheldon:)Just a few things you
may need tonight.
(Sheldon:)Baby oil, condoms
and, uh...
(Sheldon:)a little something I procured from the
school of pharmacology.
(Sheldon:)They say it is to Viagra as
Viagra is to a green M&M.